<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on My Resume Site</title>
    <link>https://resume.qliu.ca/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on My Resume Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://resume.qliu.ca/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Guide to Web Performance Optimization</title>
      <link>https://resume.qliu.ca/blog/a-guide-to-web-performance-optimization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://resume.qliu.ca/blog/a-guide-to-web-performance-optimization/</guid>
      <description>Web performance optimization (WPO) is a critical aspect of web development that focuses on improving the speed, responsiveness, and overall user experience of a website. A fast-loading website not only provides a better experience for users but also ranks higher in search engine results.&#xA;Why Web Performance Matters When users visit a website, they expect it to load quickly. Studies have shown that even a one-second delay in page load time can lead to a significant drop in user satisfaction and conversions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Static Site Generators</title>
      <link>https://resume.qliu.ca/blog/understanding-static-site-generators/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://resume.qliu.ca/blog/understanding-static-site-generators/</guid>
      <description>Static site generators (SSGs) are tools that compile templates and content into static HTML files. Unlike traditional dynamic websites that generate pages on the server with each request, static sites are pre-built and served directly to users, which can lead to faster load times and better security.&#xA;What is a Static Site Generator? A static site generator takes content (usually written in Markdown) and templates (often written in HTML) and combines them to generate static HTML files.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
